what's up kids I'm your
qué pasa chavalería soy vuestro chico de
favorite office boy and yes I know what you
oficina favorito y si ya sé lo que
're probably thinking when you see me with these
estaréis pensando al verme con estas
glasses and it's exactly the same thing
gafas y es exactamente lo mismo que
I would think if I opened a Javi
pensaría yo si abriera un vídeo de javi
Oliveira video and found this guy with
oliveira y me encontrara a este tío con
glasses I would say exactly what
gafas exactamente diría que hace
Superman is doing with a Marvel t-shirt
superman con una camiseta de marvel
[Music]
[Música]
Shakira confirms her relationship with Piqué
shakira confirma su relación con piqué
but before getting into the subject I'm going to thank you
pero antes de entrar en materia voy a
for the support for today's video
dar las gracias por el apoyo al vídeo de
and ask you to please subscribe to
hoy y pedir por favor que os suscriban a
my channel if it's your first time coming
mi canal si es la primera vez que venís
and you didn't know me and on this channel you
y que no me conocía y en este canal os
will find out all the gossip from the
enteraréis de todos los chismes del
world of the heart of the world of
mundo del corazón del mundo de los
celebrities of the youtubers the fact is that
famosos de los youtubers el caso es que
here there are many the CEO here you will
aquí hay muchos al ceo aquí os
find out being Hector Diaz being some
enteraréis estar héctor díaz siendo unas
things you really will be a [ __ ] disgusting let's
cosas realmente seréis un [__] asco a
see I'm sorry I am not an example to
ver lo siento no soy ningún ejemplo a
follow of an influential person who has
seguir de persona influyente que tiene
affection for his followers I consider that we are
cariño por sus seguidores considero que
disgusting but we remain both me and
damos asco pero quedamos tanto yo como
you and I believe that the affection that we
usted y creo que el cariño que los
have is reciprocal you either that you
tenemos es recíproco ustedes tampoco que
can see me a lot but the  gossip is
me podáis ver mucho pero el chisme es el
gossip and you want to know about the gossip
chisme y queréis enterar os del chisme
so I'll tell you guys
así que yo os lo cuento ustedes
subscribe if that's the deal if akira
suscribir si ese es el trato si akira
confirmed today through her
confirmó hoy a través de su
representative specifically in a
representante en concreto en un mensaje
rather short whatsapp message part of the
de whatsapp bastante corto parte de los
rumors that had been circulating in the
rumores que se venían comentando en las
last few hours about her breakup with pique it
últimas horas sobre su ruptura con pique
really catches my attention that they take and
me llama mucho la atención que cojan y
publish the screenshot of the whatsapp this
publiquen la captura de el whatsapp esto
is the last thing I was missing to see and
ya es lo último que me faltaba por ver y
wow in a video clip streaming
vaya en un videoclip haciendo streaming
on tweet toquero energy washing his
en tweet toquero energía lavándose la
hair
cabeza
exaggerating don't be that kid the day he has to
exagerando no sea ese chaval el día que
take off his cap he's going to have to
se tenga que quitar la gorra va a tener
pick up a hammer and chisel to
que [__] un martillo y un cincel para
do it but
poder hacerlo pero
in this message they confirm the separation
en este mensaje confirman la separación
and ask for respect for their privacy for their
y piden respeto a su privacidad para sus
children well for their children not for their
hijos bueno para sus hijos no por sus
children I would really [ __ ] myself up announcing
hijos ya me jodería a anunciar un
gossip because literally shakira
cotilleo porque literalmente shakira
representative and piqué and the mother who
representante y piqué y la madre que los
gave birth to them know that when they are publishing
parió saben que cuando están publicando
this message all the networks and all the
este mensaje todas las cadenas y toda la
gossip press are going to explode
prensa del corazón va a estallar
immediately they were going to put out a lot of
inmediatamente iban a sacar muchísimo
content about this message how
contenido sobre este mensaje como le
can you ask the  full that they don't eat
puedes pedir a las llenas que no coman
meat also a few hours later
carne también algunas horas más tarde
he denied the version of the magazine
desmentía la versión de la revista
'hola' that we were commenting on in the
'hola' que la estuvimos comentando en el
last video and we were also
último vídeo y también le estuvimos
commenting on my TV channel he falsified
comentando en mi canal de tele falseó
that it is a gossip channel that I also
que es un canal de cotilleo que también
have and it seems that what
tengo y es que al parecer lo que nos
the magazine 'hola' told us was
contó la revista 'hola' era
completely inaccurate all this of
completamente inexacto todo esto por
course according to Shakira's version that I
supuesto según la versión de shakira que
have no reason to believe because I have
no tengo por qué creerme la porque
not found any indication or
tampoco encontrado ningún indicio o
proof that says otherwise according to
prueba que diga lo contrario según
Shakira the reality is that this day
shakira la realidad es que este día
she called the ambulance and they left in an
llamó a la ambulancia y se fueron en
ambulance because her father who comes
ambulancia porque su padre que viene de
to Spain from time to time with her mother
vez en cuando a españa junto a su madre
of course and stays for a few days to
por supuesto y se queda unos días de
visit, took a tremendous hit he
visita se pegó una ostia tremenda ya se
fell and had a tremendous hit
cayó y se fue una tremenda señora [__]
and they had to take
y se lo tuvieron que llevar de urgencia
the man urgently they are obviously 90 years old and it
al hombre evidentemente tienen 90 años y
is logical that they called the ambulance that
es lógico que llamen a la ambulancia que
is here she got in the ambulance
está aquí se montó en la ambulancia
obviously to accompany him after
evidentemente para acompañarlo después
all the blows and all the
de todos los golpes y todos los
bruises that we have been analyzing in
moratones que hemos estado analizando en
the last few weeks this marathon
las últimas semanas este maratón me
seems quite real to me okay  Amber I
resulta bastante real vale amber
really can't, I mean no, I don't think it's
no puedo de verdad o sea no no me parece
appropriate to address the issue as I'm
apropiado tratar el tema como lo estoy
addressing it today. Shakira's father is
tratando hoy el padre de shakira es
William Mebarak. He and his wife
william mebarak tanto él como su esposa
often travel to Barcelona seasonally
suelen viajar por temporada a barcelona
to visit their daughter and grandchildren. He is
a visitar a su hija y a sus nietos él es
a writer over 90 years old.
un escritor de más de 90 años de edad
After seeing the blow to the face and
después de ver el golpe en la cara y
analyzing so many fake bruises
analizar tantos moretones falsos
lately, I can say that the blow to
últimamente puedo decir que el golpe de
William Mebarak, Shakira's father, does
william mebarak padre de shakira sí que
look real and very strong by the way. And
se ve real y muy fuerte por cierto y
taking into account that the gentleman is 90 years old, it
teniendo en cuenta los 90 años de edad
is completely
que tiene el señor es completamente
normal to call an ambulance
normal que se llame a una ambulancia
after suffering a fall like this.
después de sufrir una caída como esta
Likewise, after seeing her
igualmente después de ver caer a su
father fall, it would also be normal for Shakira to
padre también sería normal que shakira
suddenly become very nervous and
de repente estuviera muy nerviosa e
even have an
incluso que le diera un ataque de
anxiety attack. What would happen to me and with
ansiedad a mí lo que me haría y con
so many meals? Don't get me wrong.
muchísimas comidas no me malinterpretéis
Thank you for this out of context and
gracias de esta sacada de contexto y de
this fake news. It's like the media and
esta noticia fake es como los medios y
the disgusting press. This heartfelt thing that
el asco de prensa este de corazón que
we have, which I have told you on many
tenemos que ya os he dicho en muchas
occasions that it is not the law and that there is
ocasiones que no la ley y que no le hay
nothing to it, that you do not watch TV.  don't go
nada que no veáis la tele que no vayáis
to the cinema to see it, I was just
al cine que veáis yo tuve nada más en
joking, it got a little out of
broma broma se me ha ido un poco de las
hand, but look at the
manos pero fijaros que la prensa del
gossip press, the journalists who said so, they were
corazón los periodistas que afirmaron se
even giving details of things
daban incluso detalles de frases que
Shakira said to the nurses in
decía shakira a los enfermeros dentro de
the ambulance, I'd be pissed off. I
la ambulancia que ya me jodería yo me
asked myself yesterday when I told what
pregunte ayer cuando conté lo que estaba
the press was saying, how the hell did they know
diciendo la prensa como [__] sabían
what they had said here, the good stuff, maybe
lo que habían hablado aquí de lo bueno a
anyone who was
lo mejor cualquiera que estuviera por
there heard it without malice and
allí pues lo escuchó sin maldad y se lo
told the press, but that's how they are, I mean, it does
contó a la prensa pero es que son así o
n't matter whether you make a mountain out of a
sea no importa hacer una montaña de un
molehill or just make up
grano de arena o inventarse directamente
a fairy tale.
un cuento de hadas también se ha
In the last few hours, the issue
desmentido en las últimas horas el tema
of Pique's alleged lover
de que la supuesta amante de pique
being the mother of this Pablo Javi
hubiera sido la madre del tal pablo javi
on opap and Gabi has also been denied. In fact, what they are
en opap y gabi de hecho lo que están
saying is that the photograph that was
diciendo es que la fotografía que se
shared, the person they are
compartió a la persona que están
pointing at in those photographs, will not be the
señalando en esas fotografías no será la
mother of the 17-year-old soccer player's kid, it
madre del chaval del futbolista de 17
would be the sister, it is the sister,
años sería la hermana es la hermana
so there are three possibilities
entonces aquí caben tres posibilidades
that arise in my mind, one that it was
que se me plantean a mí una que fuera
all completely false and pulled out of
todo completamente falso y sacado de la
thin air  that pique would not have hooked up
manga que pique no se hubiera enrollar
with the mother or the sister or
ni con la madre ni con la hermana ni con
anyone who has to do with this soccer
nadie que tenga que ver con este
player 2 that he has hooked up with
futbolista 2 que se haya enrollado con
the mother but she is not the one in the photos and 3
la madre pero no es la de las fotos y 3
that he has actually hooked up with the
que en realidad se ha enrollado en la
sister I sincerely believe that the
hermana yo creo sinceramente que los
shots are not going for anyone related to
tiros no van por nadie relacionado con
this kid I mean the
este chaval me refiero al futbolista
young soccer player I think that what would be most
jovencito yo creo que lo que más
correct would be that they were already separated
cuadraría sería ya estuvieran separados
acting in front of the public that they are a
actuando de cara al público que son
couple that it was an open couple there are
pareja que fuera una pareja abierta
also rumors out there I do not know if they are
también se rumorea por ahí no sé si lo
going to confirm it or not or three in the case
van a confirmar o no o tres en el caso
of infidelity that it was someone
de ser infidelidad que fuera alguien
anonymous talks to you about a stewardess they talk
anónima te habla de una azafata se habla
about models the kid I sincerely
de modelos el chaval yo sinceramente
believe four times that I have seen
creo cuatro veces que he visto de
interviews that the
entrevista tampoco que lo haya notado el
smartest in the class has not noticed it but it would seem like
más listo de la clase pero me parecería
complete nonsense
una completa burrada haberse enrollado
to me to have hooked up with a person within the club let's see I want to remind you that it is also to show the previous video how piqué said that he liked kicking a ball more than dancing the waka waka la shakira [Music] priorities everyone has priorities in life there are people who start
en la vida hay gente que empieza a
eating the ice cream  on the
comerse el helado por el lado de la
cookie side and there are other people who start
galleta y hay otra gente que empieza a
eating the ice cream on the
comerse el helado por el lado del
chocolate side and yet there is also
chocolate y sin embargo existe también
a small portion of people who
una mínima parte de personas que
simply destroy the cookie and the
simplemente destrozan la galleta y el
ice cream to see if they have won the
helado para ver si les ha tocado el
prize inside. In the statement that she
premio de dentro en el comunicado que
published on her twitter account in both
publicó en su cuenta de twitter tanto en
English and Spanish, she explains what
inglés como en español explica lo
happened to her father although he only
sucedido a su padre aunque él lo único
denies it so if it seems strange
que desmiente por lo que si se hace raro
that she comes out to deny her
que salga a desmentir su ataque de
anxiety attack but does not do the same with the
ansiedad pero no haga lo mismo con los
rumors of an alleged infidelity of
rumores de una presunta infidelidad de
her ex-partner Gerard Piqué it is
su ex pareja gerard piqué sí que es
true that she would not have to do it I understand that she
verdad que no tendría por qué hacerlo
denied the supposed anxiety attack to calm down
ansiedad lo haya desmentido para calmar
and so that her fans or people who
y que no se preocupen su fan o gente que
appreciate her do not worry and that the intimate subject the
la aprecia y que el tema íntimo el tema
personal subject the subject of whether she has been
personal el tema de si le han puesto la
cheated on or not, she keeps it to herself because she does not
cornamenta o no se lo reserve porque no
want to give explanations and does not want to
quiera dar explicaciones y no quiera
enter the world of characters who
entrar en el mundo de personajes que
sell out or who create controversy with their
venden o que hacen polémica con su vida
intimate life. I really do not believe that if we
íntima realmente tampoco creo si nos
put ourselves at the same level there would be no
ponemos así al mismo nivel no tendría
reason to have given explanations as to whether it is
por qué haber dado explicaciones de si
done for or not for each person, no matter how
se hace para o no cada persona por muy
famous and media-savvy, she has every
famosa y mediática que sea tiene todo el
right to
derecho
publish whatever part of her life she wants. I'm
se publica la parte de su vida que le dé
saying there are a lot of people who
la gana ya digo hay mucha gente que
talk about how the couple broke up a
habla de que la pareja estaba rota desde
long time ago and that they were more or less putting on a show. There are other people who talk about an open relationship and that there would be no infidelity whatsoever. In fact, according to what they say on Telecinco, we've
según cuentan en telecinco
just gotten out of one, we're getting into
acabamos de salir de una nos metemos en
others, we're already criticizing the guy who
otras ya estamos criticando al tío que
said what happened to the mother of that
afirmo lo de la madre del muchacho ese
17-year-old boy from Barcelona and the guy from
de 17 años de barcelona y al del
this newspaper, the place where
periódico este el sitio donde trabaja la
Laura Fa works, for the
laura fa por el tema del ataque de
anxiety attack. Let's put on the table
ansiedad y vamos a poner sobre la mesa
the possibilities that Viva la Vida gives us.
las posibilidades que nos da viva la
According to what
vida según han estado diciendo el
Telecinco collaborators on Viva la
colaboradores de telecinco en viva la
Vida have been saying, people close to Gerard Piqué
vida gente del entorno de gerard piqué
would be there and also Shakira's by the way, they
estaría y también de shakira por cierto
would be affirming that there has been no
estarían afirmando que no han existido
cheating, that there would be no infidelity,
cuernos que no habría infidelidad por lo
therefore, reading between the lines, what we
tanto leyendo entre líneas lo que
can deduce would be an open relationship,
podemos deducir sería una pareja abierta
although the couple no longer existed, in this
aunque la pareja ya no existía en este
case, a divorce will not be necessary
caso no va a ser necesario un divorcio
since although the couple lived together for more
ya que aunque la pareja convivió por más
than  13 years never married but even so
de 13 años nunca se casó pero aún así al
having children will have to reach an
tener hijos tendrán que llegar a un
agreement on custody Shakira could
acuerdo sobre la custodia shakira podría
even be thinking about changing her
estar pensando incluso en cambiar su
place of residence since the only
lugar de residencia ya que la única
reason why she lived in Spain was her
razón por la que vivía en españa era su
partner Piqué however she
pareja piqué sin embargo ella por aquí
is a lonely person here who has been
es una persona solitaria a la que se le
seen leaving the house little all the
ha visto salir poco de casa todos los
few relatives who come to visit her
pocos familiares que van a visitarla
spend more time in her residence in
pasar más tiempo en su residencia en
Florida it would be a possibility that she could
florida sería una posibilidad que podría
consider since she would be in a place much
considerar ya estaría en un lugar mucho
closer to her friends family and
más cercano a sus amigos familiares ya
job opportunities since the entire
posibilidades de trabajo pues toda la
Spanish music industry is
industria de la música en español se
located there also remember that a
encuentra allí además recordemos que
few days ago it was reported that Shakira
hace unos días se informó que shakira
would be a few steps away from going to trial
estaría a pocos pasos de ir a un juicio
for alleged tax fraud making
por presunto fraude fiscal haciendo por
more than 14.5 million dollars
más de 14,5 millones de dólares según
apparently for managing some income
parece por gestionar algunos ingresos a
through other countries such as Malta or
través de otros países como malta o
Luxembourg and it would have been possible to verify
luxemburgo y se habría podido comprobar
that despite the fact that she travels
que a pesar de que ella viaja
constantly her place of residence
constantemente su lugar de residencia
would be Barcelona all this between 2012 and
sería barcelona todo esto entre 2012 y
2014 when according to the singer she resided in
2014 cuando según la cantante residía en
her house in the Bahamas and only visited
su casa en las bahamas y solo visitaba a
her boyfriend for seasons  In Barcelona you already
su novio por temporadas en barcelona ya
know that here in Spain the people who
sabéis que aquí en españa la gente que
earn have to write if people want to
gana disponer escribe si la gente quiere
earn a lot of money the self-employed in
ganar mucho dinero los autónomos en
general here in Spain have no sense of
general aquí en españa no tienen sentido
taxes I'm not going to go into much
los impuestos no voy a entrar mucho en
depth because the video is not going to
profundidad porque el vídeo no va a
be about that but here in Spain they
tratar sobre eso pero aquí en españa
directly assault us they assault us
directamente nos asaltan nos asaltan
because we are idiots who let ourselves be
porque somos [__] que nos dejamos
assaulted and after they assault us we
asaltar que luego de que nos asalta
go back to vote for the same
volvemos a votar a los mismos partidos
old parties who assault us at the
de siempre que nos asaltan en la
gas station on the electricity bill and in
gasolinera en la factura de la luz y en
a lot of places and the self-employed the
un montón de sitios y los autónomos en
moment they start collecting don't
el momento que empiezan a cobrar tampoco
believe that millions are looted with
te creas que millones son saqueados con
no more and no less than half of their
ni más ni menos que la mitad de sus
income when you are self-employed at the
ingresos cuando tú eres autónomo en el
moment you are collecting
momento que estás cobrando
56 10 89 thousand euros they are already taking away
56 10 89 mil euros ya te están quitando
half more or less exactly but come on
la mitad más o menos exacto pero vamos
spark more or less of what is
chispa más o menos de lo que esté
generating incredible right apart from
generando increíble verdad a parte de
taking a percentage if you sell a
quitarte un porcentaje de si vendes una
house if you earn money in the stock market or in
casa si ganas dinero en bolsa o en
Christ's currency I will never defend not
cristo' moneda yo nunca defenderé no
paying taxes but I think that
pagar impuestos pero yo creo que habría
a higher amount should be paid  reasonable and that it was
que pagar una cifra más razonable y que
really necessary because then we
realmente hiciera falta porque luego
see what they spend the money on here
vemos en lo que se gastan aquí el dinero
and our faces come well they laugh I do
y se vienen nuestras caras bueno se ríen
n't know Shakira's legal team
no se me ha el equipo legal de shakira
says that Shakira is obviously
dice que shakira evidentemente es
innocent and that her conduct in terms of
inocente y que su conducta en cuanto a
tax payments is impeccable that
los pagos fiscales es intachable que
as soon as she found out she had to pay an
apenas supo que debía pagar un monto
extra amount she did it immediately so
extra lo hizo de inmediato por lo que
today she has no debt with the
hoy en día no tiene ninguna deuda con el
Spanish state that's what I'm telling you
estado español es lo que os digo
at this point or Shakira as a
llegados a este punto o shakira como
Spaniard or having residency in
española o teniendo la residencia en
Spain would not be exempt from having her
españa no estaría exenta de que le
taken away because the word would be that they
quiten porque la palabra sería que le
take away like what happens to many
quiten al igual que les pasa a muchos
YouTubers 50 percent of what she
youtuber el 50 por ciento de lo que
generates and that's a point to go to
genere y eso es un puntazo para irse a
Florida also if you don't have anything here
florida también si no tienes nada aquí
that ties you down and that ties you down really hard
que te amarre y que te amarre de [__]
and you can do low deciding
y puedes hacer bajo decidiendo en
anywhere well the truth is that
cualquier parte pues la verdad es que
Spain is one of the worst options for
españa es una de las peores opciones a
me for example it ties me down my children have
mí por ejemplo me amarra en mis hijos
spent all the years of their lives
llevan todos los años de su vida
residing here and Shakira themselves
residiendo aquí y los mismos shakira
takes this into account and if she stays in
esto lo tiene en cuenta y si se queda en
Spain is for its children allowing them to take
españa es por sus hijos permitiendo que
out Florida in addition to being very
le saquen florida además de ser muy
convenient for his work it is one of
conveniente para su trabajo es uno de
the states with the lowest taxes
los estados con los impuestos más bajos
in the US so I tell you that it would be a
de eeuu por lo que ya os digo que sería
pretty good option even if he is not
bastante buena opción aunque no esté
married as a couple of so many years they
casado como pareja de tantos años igual
should still decide what to do with the fortune
deben decidir qué hacer con la fortuna
of more than 700 million euros that they
de más de 700 millones de euros que
accumulate between both although
acumulan entre ambos aunque de forma
individually each one already has it by not being
individual cada uno ya tiene al no estar
married their individual fortunes are
casado sus fortunas individuales están
clear however in many businesses
claras sin embargo en muchos negocios
they are partners and many properties in the name
son socio y muchas propiedades a nombre
of both including the sport team
de ambos incluyendo el equipo de sport
regarding the alleged infidelity that has not
sobre la presunta infidelidad que
yet been denied or
todavía ni se ha desmentido ni se ha
confirmed but that draws attention I already
confirmado pero que llama la atención ya
told you to deny one thing and the other I
os digo que desmienta una cosa y la otra
left watching the game that he has brought
la dejé viendo el juego que se ha traído
with his last video clip the same
con su último videoclip lo mismo
denying that with the father is a
desmentir eso con lo del padre es una
way of indirectly confirming
manera de confirmar indirectamente lo de
the infidelity I'm going to leave you with this
la infidelidad os voy a dejar con este
guy in which some girls give us more
tipo en el que unas chicas nos dan más
information that she has discovered that
datos que ha descubierto de que
clearly the song from Felicito is
claramente la canción desde felícito va
for him what nobody has seen in the
para él lo que nadie ha visto en el
video clip of Felicita
videoclip de felicita
with Grant and that  I like to handle the
con grant y que me gusta manejar el
jockey the lyrics everything that we have
jockey la letra todo lo que hemos hecho
all done until now but I have realized
todos hasta ahora pero me ha dado cuenta
a detail that I am not in the
de un detalle que no lo estoy en el
protector and that I think that
protector y que yo creo que les ha dado
nobody has realized
cuenta nadie
first explained for example there is
primero explicaron por ejemplo
a real evil or rather very well this
hay un auténtico mal o sea muy bien esto
had that it will sting you when I remember
tenía que te va a picar cuando recuerde
how we ate chop I chopped badly
cómo nos comíamos picar piqué mal
until here everything seems a clear
hasta aquí todo parece una clara
reference to her now ex-husband but pay attention
referencia a su ya exmarido pero atentos
to the end of the video to those
al final del vídeo a esos segundos
final seconds in which the song ends and we have
finales en los que termina la canción y
all closed and then we have
ya todos hemos cerrado y entonces hemos
closed the video and we continue seeing each other
cerrado el vídeo y nos seguimos viendo
more because the song has ended
más porque la canción ha finalizado
pay attention to Shakira's final gesture with which she
atentos al gesto final de shakira con el
closes this video clip
que cierra este videoclip
attentive
atentos
weightlifting and monkeys this
levantamiento de pesas y monitos esto
may seem like something casual no but if we
puede parecer algo casual no pero si nos
go to Instagram generate that we see
vamos al instagram generarte que vemos
that it was done look at her photos raising
que se hizo miran sus fotos levantando
eyebrows and putting on pouts
cejas y poniendo morritos
she discovered why all these
ella descubrió porque era todo estos
horizons were with her children she said it was
horizontes con sus hijos dijo que era
a joke with a partner of hers in the
una broma con un compañero suyo en el
expense but let's go with these here she makes it
gasto pero vamos con estos aquí la deja
clear that the song and the video clip is
claro que la canción y el videoclip está
full of references to her ex María ex-
lleno de referencias as a su ex maría ex
partner is far from giving bite he is one of the
pareja está lejos de dar pique es uno de
players  of the most controversial football has gotten into
los jugadores de fútbol más polémicas ha
lately he has been criticized
metido últimamente ha sido criticado
because people said that he was a bad
porque la gente decía que nos mal
loser dedicating his victory to the
perdedor dedicándole su victoria al
opposing team also for commenting on
equipo contrario también por opinar de
a political conflict in his region
un conflicto político de su región
Catalonia while then he presents himself
cataluña mientras que luego se presenta
to represent Spain in various
a representar a españa en varias
sporting competitions such as the
competencias deportivas como es el
World Cup no that you already know that
mundial de fútbol no que ya sabéis que
he is from the Spanish national team also
él es de la selección española también
recently he was accused of mediating
recientemente se le acusó de mediar a
through his company to carry the
través de su empresa para llevar la
Spanish Super Cup which is a match
supercopa de españa que es un partido
between the winner of the league and the winner
entre el ganador de la liga y el ganador
of the King's Cup Saudi Arabia for
de la copa del rey arabia saudita por lo
which he was questioned because being a
cual fue cuestionado porque al ser un
player there could be a conflict of
jugador podría haber un conflicto de
interest he has also boasted a lot about
intereses también ha alardeado mucho de
his fortune bragging that his
su fortuna presumiendo de que su
assets are larger than the Spanish
patrimonio sea más grande que el español
FC and you know that people usually get
fc y ya sabéis que a la gente esto le
very annoyed by this in a tweet in which
suele molestar mucho de un tuit
he directly showed his
que él directamente enseñaba su
transfer in the bank or in other words the day he
transferencia en el banco o sea el día
received his salary the transfer of
que cobró el sueldo la transferencia de
what I receive I think I remember that he said that it
lo que cobro creo recordar que dijo que
was one of the many salaries that he had
era uno de los tantos sueldos que tenía
during the year and in this case it was an
durante el año y en este caso era un
income of 2 or  3 million euros - I think it
ingreso de 2 o 3 millones de euros- creo
was in this click I'm going to put that I don't
que era en este clic voy a poner que no
know if it has a copy and my editor is going to
sé si tiene copia y mi editor le va a
put some more appropriate music so that
poner una musiquita más adecuada para
the copy doesn't jump we can see that we don't
que no salte el copy podemos ver que no
know if in other areas the couple
sabemos si en otros ámbitos la pareja
would have chemistry but in the dance
tendría química pero en el baile desde
certainly not
luego que no
[Music]
[Música]
youtube to explode of course direct
youtube de explotar por supuesto directo
without stopping tried we are already live
sin parar probó ya estamos en vivo
prevention
prevención
dogs that dance and more subscribe to
perros que bailan y más suscríbete a
climb okay now yes now I'm taller you
escalar vale ahora si ahora soy más alto
won't regret it we have
no te arrepentirás tenemos entre la
a little joy among the people you will be
gente un poquito de alegría serás
the dogs that dance and more subscribe
los perros que bailan y más suscríbete
alcalá okay now yes now yes taller you won't
alcalá vale ahora sí ahora sí más alto
regret it we have that among the
no te arrepentirás tenemos que entre la
people a little joy you will be what is
gente un poquito de alegría serás
clear is that at least
lo que sí queda claro es que al menos
the public displays of affection always
las muestras de afecto públicas siempre
went more on Shakira's side than
iban más del lado de shakira a pique que
the other way around because she practically
al revés pues ella prácticamente le
idolized him in some messages on
idolatraba en algunos mensajes de redes
social networks and classified him as not only
sociales y lo catalogaba como no solo de
the best partner but the best
ser la mejor pareja sino el mejor
professional one of the last
profesional una de las últimas
photographs that the couple has together
fotografías que tiene la pareja juntos
was the one they uploaded at the end of the year where
fue la que subieron el fin de año donde
the  two apparently very
salen los dos aparentemente muy
affectionate and it seems that there are
acaramelados y parece ser que no hay
no problems in this
ningún tipo de problemas en esta
relationship at the moment the footballer
relación de momento el futbolista no se
has not commented on the subject where he has been
ha pronunciado sobre el tema donde sí se
seen quite frequently it has been in
ha visto con bastante frecuencia ha sido
the private rooms of two clubs
los reservados de dos discotecas en
specifically Patrón and Blin Blin and according to what is being
concreto patrón y blin blin y según está
reported informally since by the way
informando informal ya que por cierto de
I do trust this publication I could be
esta publicación sí que me fío me puedo
wrong but in my experience
equivocar pero en mi experiencia
following the news in this medium that I
siguiendo noticias en este medio que lo
do through the news we comment
hago a través de las noticias comentamos
from the heart and such according to Lee Hay reports it
del corazón y tal según informa lee haya
is a fact that the couple is
es un hecho que la pareja se está
separating and their teams of lawyers
separando y sus equipos de abogados
would be reaching an agreement to
estarían poniéndose de acuerdo para
agree on the separation of assets and
acordar la separación de bienes y la
custody of the children here I will be
custodia de los hijos por aquí os estaré
putting you to remind you of a publication
poniendo para recordaros una publicación
from April 9 of this same year where
del 9 de abril de este mismo año donde
for the first time the singer made a
por primera vez la cantante hacía una
reference to this song that has all
referencia a esta canción que tiene toda
the appearances well almost confirmed not
la pinta bueno casi confirmadísimo no
confirmed that it is dedicated to Piqué and up to
confirmadísimo que va dedicada a piqué y
here today this is all there is let's
hasta aquí de hoy esto es todo lo que
wait and see if the footballer gets
hay esperemos a ver si el futbolista se
involved and confirms the same thing that Shakira has said
moja y confirma lo mismo que ha dicho
sources that claim to be close to
shakira fuentes que dicen ser cercanas a
Piqué say that he would not be very happy
pique dicen que no estaría muy contento
with the statement and with the way of
con la declaración y con la forma de
announce what Shakira had today
anunciar lo que ha tenido shakira hoy
that I would be quite in disagreement so
que estaría bastante en desacuerdo así
we will see what happens
que ya veremos a ver qué es lo que pasa
and how she acts in the next few hours if she doesn't
y cómo actúa en las próximas horas si no
say anything else because here we have the
dice más nada pues aquí tenemos el
final result of Jara in the air the
resultado final de jara en el aire las
speculations about a possible
especulaciones sobre una posible
infidelity but whatever happens
infidelidad pero pase lo que pase
we will be aware of the gossip
nosotros estaremos pendientes del chisme
and above all you are going to love this
y sobre todo esto os va a encantar
because I am going to end the video with
porque os voy a finalizar el vídeo con
some glasses kisses family see you
unos vasos besos familia nos vemos
tomorrow well no we will probably see each other the
mañana bueno no seguramente nos veamos
same okay
el mismo vale
that
eso
youtube of exploding
youtube de explotar
direct without stopping but we are already
directo sin parar pero ya estamos en
live pressure
vivo presión
dogs that dance and more subscribe to
perros que bailan y más suscríbete a
climb okay now yes now kneading
escalar vale ahora sí ahora sí amasando
you will not regret it we have to between the
no te arrepentirás tenemos que entre la
people a little the gallery you will be
gente un poquito la galería serás